Improved By : FidelPerez Subtitle By : explosiveskull Sub Upload Date : August 22 , 2018
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
( SIGHS ) Come on , Peter .
Wake up . Peter . Wake up .
Here 's your suit .
Do you know if your sister slept in her room last night ?
I don 't know .
Come on , Peter . Get up .
( GRUNTS )
Oh , Charlie . For God 's sake , come on !
It was freezing last night !
That 's how you get pneumonia .
That 's okay .
Okay , come on . Let 's go . We 're late .
Your mother 's in the car already .
ANNIE : ( CLEARS THROAT ) Um ...
It 's heartening to see so many strange new faces here today .
Um , I know my mom would be very touched
and probably a little suspicious ... ( CHUCKLES )
um , to see this turnout . So .
My mother was a very secretive and private woman .
She had private rituals ,
private friends , private anxieties .
It honestly feels like a betrayal
just to be standing here talking about her .
She was a very difficult woman to read .
If you ever thought you knew what was going on with her ,
and God forbid you tried to confront that .
But when her life was unpolluted ,
she could be the sweetest , warmest ,
most loving person in the world .
She was also incredibly stubborn ,
which maybe , explains me .
( SCRIBBLING ON PAPER )
You could always count on her to always have the answer .
( CHARLIE CLICKS TONGUE )
ANNIE : And if she ever was mistaken ,
and well , that was your opinion ...
- ( CLICKS TONGUE ) - And you were wrong .
There aren 't nuts in that ?
- No . - Good .
Does that have nuts ? ' Cause we don 't have the EpiPen .
STEVE : I know .
Hello , Rexy ! Good dog .
Shoes off , everybody .
Charlie , shoes off .
It does feel weird .
( SOFTLY ) Yeah .
Should I be sadder ?
You should be whatever you are . It 'll come .
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
Hey , how 's it going ?
Mmm , just working .
Taking a break from avoiding the show .
So , you still toiling away at the hospice ?
Yeah , between this and the , uh , preschool .
So what 's our deadline now ? Seven months ?
- Six and a half . - Ooh , coming up .
Any ideas for titles ?
- ( ♫
STRUMMING GUITAR ♫ ) - ( TV PLAYING )
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
Come in .
Hey ...
- Goodnight , kiddo . - Goodnight .
Are you , uh ... Are you feeling okay about everything ?
Yeah . Fine .
A little sad ?
Mmm ... (
CHUCKLES )
Yeah , I get it . I know .
- Goodnight . - Night .
STEVE : Love you .
ANNIE : Who 's this ?
That 's Grandma ?
You know you were her favorite , right ?
Even when you were a little baby ,
she wouldn 't let me feed you
because she needed to feed you .
Drove me crazy .
She wanted me to be a boy .
You know , I was a tomboy when I was growing up .
I hated dresses and dolls and pink .
Who 's gonna take care of me ?
( SCOFFS ) Um , excuse me .
You don 't think I 'm gonna take care of you ?
But when you die .
Well , then ...
Dad will take care of you .
Or Peter .
You never cried as a baby .
You know that ?
Even when you were born .
Did you feel like you wanted to cry today ?
You think it might feel like a relief ?
( KISSING )
Goodnight , sweetheart .
( SIGHS )
Mom ?
( SWITCH CLICKS )
( EXHALES DEEPLY )
I just scared myself in the workshop .
With ... With what ?
( CHUCKLES )
No .
Are you done ?
Almost .
So , maybe we finish the toy after the quiz .
What do you think ?
- Okay . - Okay .
( THUDS )
- ( ALL
EXCLAIMING ) - Oh , my God ! What was that ?
( STUDENTS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY )
TEACHER : So , if we go by the rule
that the hero is undone by his fatal flaw ,
what is Heracles ' flaw ?
BRIDGET : Arrogance .
Okay . Why ?
Because he literally refuses to look at all the signs
that are literally handed to him the entire play .
TEACHER : Okay , interesting .
- ( CELL PHONE
VIBRATES ) - So he thinks he has control .
But let 's all remember ,
Sophocles wrote the oracle so that it was unconditional ,
meaning , Heracles never had any choice , right ?
So does that make it more tragic or less tragic
that if he has a choice ?
- BOY : Less . - Okay .
- Why ? - Because .
TEACHER : Care to weigh in , Peter ?
Um , about which part ?
GIRL : I think it 's more tragic
because if it 's all just inevitable ,
then that means that the characters had no hope .
They never had hope
because they 're all just , like , hopeless .
They 're all like pawns
in this horrible , hopeless machine .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGS )
( DOOR OPENS )
- STEVE : Hello ! - ANNIE : Hi !
( DOOR CLOSES )
Did you go up in my mom 's room ?
No .
Mmm . Door was open .
( PHONE RINGING IN DISTANCE )
PETER : Hello ?
Sorry . I know it 's irrational .
- No problem . - Thank you .
Hey , Dad . It 's the cemetery .
About what ?
Let me see .
Hello ? Yes .
What does that mean ?
Desecrated ?
But it 's only been a week .
( SIGHS )
Yes , okay , yes . Sure .
All right . I understand . Yes ...
Uh , why don 't I call you back ? Yes . Goodbye .
What was it ?
Uh , just some billing crap .
Okay , well , I 'm , uh ... I 'm gonna go see a movie .
Okay .
( WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH )
TRANSLATOR : ( IN ENGLISH ) He would say
" I 'm a burden , I 'm a burden , I 'm a burden . "
( WOMAN SPEAKING SPANISH )
TRANSLATOR : And I would tell him , " No , no . "
TRANSLATOR : But yes , he was a burden .
Now we 've set aside some time for any newcomers
who might like to speak .
So , anyone .
If it 's your first or second time with us ,
the floor is open .
Yes . Would you like to ...
Maybe not .
Okay . No pressure .
My name 's Annie .
ALL : Hi , Annie .
My mom died a week ago .
So I 'm just here for trying it .
I have a lot of resistance to things like this ,
but I came to these a couple years ago .
Well , I was forced to come and I guess it , um ...
I guess it helped . So , um ...
My mom was old and she wasn 't all together there at the end .
And we were pretty much estranged before that ,
so it really wasn 't a huge blow .
But I did love her .
And she didn 't have an easy life .
She had DID , which became extreme at the end .
And dementia .
And my father died when I was a baby from starvation ,
um , because he had psychotic depression
and he starved himself ,
which I 'm sure was just as pleasant as it sounds .
And then there 's my brother .
My older brother had schizophrenia
and when he was 16
he hanged himself in my mother 's bedroom
and of course the suicide note blamed her
accusing her of putting people inside him . So .
( SIGHS )
That was my mom 's life .
And then she lived in our house
at the end before hospice .
We weren 't even talking before that .
I mean , we were and then we weren 't .
And then we were .
She 's completely manipulative .
Until my husband finally enforced a no-contact rule ,
which lasted until I got pregnant with my daughter .
I didn 't let her anywhere near me
when I had my first , my son ,
which is why I gave her my daughter ,
who she immediately stabbed her hooks into .
And I just ... I felt guilty again .
I felt guilty again .
When she got sick ,
not that she was really even my mom at the end ,
and not that she would ever feel guilty about anything .
And I just don 't want to put any more stress on my family .
I 'm not even really sure if they could ...
Could give me that support .
And I just ... I just feel like ...
I just sometimes feel like it 's all ruined .
( SOBBING )
And then I realize that I am to blame .
Or not that I 'm to blame ,
but I am blamed ! I 'm ...
MAN : And what do you think you feel blamed for ?
I don 't know .
MAN # 1 : ( ON TV ) Hey , what 's going on in town
anyway , Mister ? A convention or something ?
MAN # 2 : What ?
MAN # 1 : Well , those clothes you 're wearing .
I talked to a guy this morning
who was wearing the same kind of outfit .
MAN # 2 : Maybe it 's the guy you 're looking for , huh ?
MAN # 3 : You spoke to him ?
What did he tell you ? Where did he go ?
MAN # 1 : Hey , what 's the matter with you ?
- Hey , take your hands off me . - ( PHONE
VIBRATES )
MAN # 3 : You will tell me what he said to you !
MAN # 1 : Well why should I ?
Hey , who do you think you are anyway ?
( INDISTINCT ARGUMENT )
MAN # 1 : He came in with the dog tags !
Wanted to know about the address
and I told him how to find it .
MAN # 3 : Where ?
( CLICKING TONGUE )
( CONTINUES CLICKING TONGUE )
( CHAIR CREAKING )
( CELL PHONE VIBRATES )
Hey , um , do you think I could maybe borrow
one of the cars tonight ?
Why ? Where are you going ?
Oh , just like a school barbecue thing .
Oh , so you 're not eating with us ?
No , I was still gonna eat here .
Well , you can eat there if you want . I just didn 't ...
No , no , no . I 'm gonna eat here . I just , I ...
Just be going to hang out .
No drinking ?
We 're not even old enough to get drinks if we wanted to .
Well , that 's a crock . I 'm just asking if you 're drinking .
Well , I just answered no .
You gonna take your sister ?
Uh ... Does she want to go ?
( SIGHING ) Have you asked her ?
Charlie ?
( CLICKS TONGUE )
ANNIE : Charlie !
( ANNIE SIGHS )
I mean , what are you doing ? Leaving the house barefoot ?
Are you some kind of idiot ?
You can 't roam around with no shoes and no coat .
- I want Grandma . - Oh .
Oh , what ? You 're angry with me now ?
You are going to this ... Hey , socks off .
You 're going to this party with your brother .
CHARLIE : What party ?
Some school hangout with other kids .
CHARLIE : That 's okay .
No , it 's not okay . You 're going .
- Why ? - Because it 'll be fun .
Because you 'll get to hang out with other kids .
- With who ? - With your ...
With your brother . With other kids .
- Fine . - Good . You 're going .
- She 's going with you . - Great .
Now this really means no drinking .
Yeah , I really wasn 't going to .
( CHARLIE CLICKING TONGUE )
( CONTINUES CLICKING TONGUE )
( ♫ HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING ♫ )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
PETER : Whoa . Hi .
Oh . Hi .
How 's the party ?
Why ? You wanna know if you should come ?
Uh , yeah . What do ya think ?
Either way .
Hey , do you happen to smoke at all ?
I have really good weed .
- The other room has a bong . - Sick .
Do you wanna wait out here for a second ?
- No . - Charlie , please , just ...
It 'll be two minutes and then we can hang out .
You can draw . Please , Charlie . I 'm ...
Oh , shit , look . They 're giving out chocolate cake .
Not to everyone .
Yes to everyone . It 's a party .
- I don 't know anyone . - Nobody does .
Just walk over and stand there and they 'll give you a piece .
Hurry up . They 're gonna run out . Come on , Charlie .
Hey , guys . Peter has weed .
( ♫ MUSIC CONTINUES ♫ )
BRIDGET : That was your sister downstairs ?
- PETER : Yeah . Charlie . - ( CELL PHONE
VIBRATES )
BOY : Is your sister hot ?
I actually saw her drawing me last week .
PETER : Oh , yeah ?
Yeah . She made me look retarded .
Yeah . That 's Charlie .
( CELL PHONE VIBRATES )
( CHARLIE WHEEZING )
CHARLIE : Peter ?
Charlie . (
COUGHING )
- (
WHEEZING ) - What 's up ?
Are you okay ?
It 's hard to breathe .
What do you mean ?
I think my throat 's getting bigger .
( CHARLIE GASPING )
( GASPING )
It 's okay , Charlie . We 're almost at the hospital , okay ?
( CONTINUES GASPING )
- ( COUGHS ) - Charlie !
( BRAKES SCREECHING )
( GASPING )
( TYRES SCREECHING )
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
( GASPING )
( SIGHS ) You okay .
Okay .
ANNIE : (
WHISPERS ) Okay , good . They 're home .
STEVE : Good .
ANNIE : I 'm running out for some balsam wood .
You want anything ?
STEVE : I 'm good , sweetheart . Drive safe .
ANNIE : Okay . Back in 20 .
( DOOR OPENS )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( CAR DOOR OPENS )
( ANNIE GASPS )
( ANNIE SCREAMING )
( CONTINUES SCREAMING )
Oh , my God ! Oh , my God !
( ANNIE SOBBING )
Oh , no . I can 't , I can 't ...
(
WAILING ) I just want to die !
Oh , God . It hurts too much !
I just need to die !
( CONTINUES WAILING )
Charlie !
Oh , God .
( CONTINUES WAILING )
Oh , Charlie !
( ANNIE WAILING )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
( SIGHS )
( CLOCK TICKING )
( TEACHER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY )
Hey , are you guys friends with Becky on Facebook ?
You 're friends with Becky ?
- I said " Facebook friends . " - (
LAUGHING )
But seriously , you see her statuses , bro ?
(
CHUCKLES ) Oh , my God , dude , I know .
- Like , every ten seconds . - For real .
Oh , dude , what about , uh , fucking ... Let me hit that .
- Brian ? - Brian and his girlfriend .
He calls her something ...
He calls her something really goofy , dude . What does he ...
Oh , he calls her princess .
- (
LAUGHING ) - (
COUGHING )
Who fucking calls their girlfriend " princess " ?
What the fuck ?
Dude , he 's like ,
" I 'm picking up my princess from the airport .
Fucking eating cous ... What the fuck .
It 's couscous .
Couscous . I don 't give a shit , " ... with my princess . "
- ( COUGHS ) - You hit that shit ?
Who 's his girlfriend ?
Some , uh , some fucking stupid college chick .
Oh , damn .
I wanna fucking stupid college princess , bro .
- (
LAUGHING ) - Yeah .
Oh , hey dude . Dude , dude , dude .
Are you ... Are you all right ?
( GROANING )
I think I 'm having a ... Like a reaction .
My throat is ...
I think my throat is getting bigger .
Dude , it 's just it 's ... It 's just weed .
Chill , man . It 's all right .
Just hold my hand . Hold on .
( CRYING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( CAR ENGINE STARTS )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
- ( SEAT BELT ALARM BEEPING ) - ( ENGINE STARTS )
Uh , I 'm so sorry to chase you down .
Uh , were you not coming in , or ...
I ... No , I just , um ... I forgot something .
Oh , okay , sorry . Sorry , I just ...
I recognized you from a few months ago .
Oh , God . I feel very silly . I 'm Joan .
Hi .
(
STUTTERS ) Are you doing better ?
- What ? - After your mother ?
What ? No , no . That 's not ... ( SIGHS )
My , um ... My daughter was killed .
Oh . I 'm ... ( SIGHS )
I 'm so , so sorry .
Oh , would you like to come in with me ?
Or we could even just have a coffee .
Uh , I 'm sorry . Really , I , um ...
(
STAMMERS ) I can 't ... I really did forget something .
My son died .
Oh .
I 'm so sorry .
How old was yours ?
Thirteen .
God . That 's awful .
My son and my grandson drowned four months ago .
The little one was seven .
Oh , my God !
I 've been coming here for a couple of months now .
And it has helped .
It doesn 't make it easier obviously ,
but sometimes it makes it less lonely .
Okay .
And now I 'm about to embarrass myself but , uh ,
if you need someone to talk to ...
' Cause we all do .
If you need it .
Okay . (
SNIFFLES )
Thank you . Really .
Okay .
- ( SEAT BELT ALARM BEEPING ) - ( ENGINE STARTS )
Bye-bye .
( EXHALES )
- Hey . - Hey .
- ( SIGHS ) I 'm going to bed . - Where were you ?
At the movies . Gonna go to bed .
Okay . I 'll come up with you .
Okay .
ANNIE : ( EXHALES ) I 'll be right back .
No you won 't . You 're taking the blanket .
I can 't sleep .
It 's freezing out there .
Well , the heater 's up there .
Okay .
Is that okay ?
If it gets too cold , come back in .
I just need to sleep .
( TONGUE CLICKS IN DISTANCE )
- ( TONGUE CLICKS ) - ( GASPS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( BIRDS CHIRPING )
( FOOTSTEPS RECEDING )
Shit .
JOAN : Oh , Annie . You came .
It 's a little earlier than we said .
Ah , you 're perfect . Come in . Come in .
Uh , your welcome mat .
(
CHUCKLES ) Ah ! It 's kind of cute , huh ?
Yeah . My mother used to embroider ones just like that .
Did she really ? Isn 't that funny ?
Please come in . Sit .
ANNIE : First there 's the ...
The smell of something wrong .
( SOBBING ) And then the body .
Covered in black blood , like tar .
And her head wasn 't there so I couldn 't see her face .
( SOBBING ) But they were gone .
And her hands , and her little finger nails .
( SNIFFLES )
How is your relationship with your son ?
- Peter ? - Hmm .
Oh , God . Um ...
Okay , I sleepwalk .
I mean , I haven 't done it in years , but , um ...
A couple years ago , I woke up
and I was standing next to Peter in Charlie 's bed
when they shared a room .
And they were
completely covered in paint thinner .
And so was I.
From head to toe .
And I was standing there with a box of matches
and an empty can of paint thinner .
( SNIFFLES )
And I woke myself up striking the match ,
which also woke Peter up , and he started to scream .
( SNIFFLES )
And I immediately put the match out .
Like , immediately . ( SNIFFLES )
I mean , I was just as shocked as he was .
And it was impossible to convince them
that it was just sleepwalking ,
which of course it was , but ...
(
SNIFFLES ) The timing was awful .
Peter and I had gotten into this stupid quarreling phase ,
just forever arguing about nothing , such ...
Frivolous stuff .
And Peter always held it against me .
And there was nothing I can say
and nothing I can do
because it happened .
While I was asleep .
Hey ! That was quick .
Did you bike all the way here ?
Um , no . Actually my friend drove me home .
Oh , uh , by the way , Peter , have you , um ...
Have you signed up for that , uh , SAT prep course ?
PETER : I 'll do it tomorrow .
Yeah , you know what , you gotta do that
because it 's coming up .
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
Jesus Christ , Annie .
You 're not planning on letting him see that , are you ?
- Who ? - Peter .
How do you think he 's gonna feel when he sees that ?
What ? It 's not about him .
Oh , no ?
No . It 's a neutral view of the accident .
( SIGHS )
( STEVE CLEARS THROAT )
Are you , uh , are you coming down to dinner ?
I 'm making dinner .
No , I made the dinner . I came to get you .
Come , stay , whatever you want . I don 't really give a shit .
( CUTLERY CLATTERING )
This is really good , Dad .
Thanks , buddy .
( CHUCKLES )
( TAPPING )
You okay , Mom ?
What ?
Is there something on your mind ?
It just seems like there might be something you wanna say .
- STEVE : Peter ... - ANNIE : Like what ?
I mean , why would I wanna say something
so I can watch you sneer at me .
Sneer at you ? I don 't ever sneer at you .
Oh , sweetie . You don 't have to .
You get your point across .
Okay , so fine . Then say what you wanna say then .
Peter .
I don 't wanna say anything . I 've tried saying things .
Okay , so try again . Release yourself .
Oh , release you , you mean .
Yeah , fine . Release me . Just say it .
Just fucking say it !
Don 't you swear at me , you little shit !
Don 't you ever raise your voice at me !
I am your mother !
Do you understand ?
All I do is worry and slave and defend you .
And all I get back is that fucking face on your face .
So full of disdain and resentment
and always so annoyed .
Well , now your sister is dead .
And I know you miss her , and I know it was an accident
and I know you 're in pain .
And I wish I could take that away for you .
I wish I could shield you from the knowledge
that you did what you did , but your sister is dead !
She 's gone forever !
And what a waste . ( CRIES )
If it could have maybe brought us together or something .
If you could have just said , " I 'm sorry " ,
or faced up to what happened .
Maybe then we could do something with this .
But you can 't take responsibility for anything !
So now I can 't accept ...
And I can 't forgive because ...
Because nobody admits anything they 've done !
( EXHALES DEEPLY )
( SIGHS )
( ANNIE MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY )
PETER : What about you , Mom ?
She didn 't wanna go to the party .
So why was she there ?
STEVE : All right . We 're stopping this right now .
That 's it .
I said stop right now .
Fine !
Fine .
ANNIE : Joan ?
Oh ! Annie !
- Hey . - Oh ! ( LAUGHING )
- Annie ! - Hi !
Oh , my !
How are you ?
- Oh , Annie ! I 'm ... - Are you okay ?
( LAUGHS )
(
STAMMERS ) I 'm ... I am , yes . I 'm really good .
- I 'm really , really ... ( SIGHS ) - Okay .
( SIGHS ) Something 's ... Something happened , Annie ,
and I feel completely turned around .
- What happened ? - ( LAUGHS )
I don 't even know if I should say .
What do you mean ?
You 're gonna think I am crazy !
No , not at all .
Oh . Okay .
All right , come on .
I met a spiritual medium .
They were performing an open séance .
I know , I know what you 're thinking ,
but they asked me to attend .
They were bringing skeptics in and scientists .
So I went , fully skeptical .
And what I experienced there , Annie , was truly ...
Open séance ...
They brought in the spirit of a man from the 19th century .
And no , no , not in a kind of smoke and mirrors way , no .
And the man sitting next to me
was a completely cynical neurologist
and he looked permanently changed by the end of it .
No , I ... I ... I know what you 're thinking . I do .
But I ... I approached the medium afterwards
and I asked her about my son and my grandson
and she came to my apartment and she ...
( SIGHS )
She ended up performing ...
Well ... She conjured my grandson .
No , no , no , I know , I know what that smile is . I know .
Annie , Annie ... I wouldn 't believe it either ,
I didn 't believe it ,
but I heard his voice .
I felt his presence in the room .
Annie , this is real .
What are you doing right now ?
I 'm just here shopping .
Do you wanna come over ?
Oh , Annie . Please , Annie . I really think you should .
It would be everything if you came .
ANNIE : Nice mood setter .
( JOAN BREATHES DEEPLY )
Okay .
I 'm going to put my hand on the glass ,
but I 'm not going to add pressure .
You do the same .
All right .
( EXHALES DEEPLY )
Louis ...
Louis , are you here ? It 's Grandma .
Louis , if you are here with us ,
please just try and slide the glass .
Louis , if you 're here ...
( GASPS )
Hi , Louis !
- (
LAUGHING ) Hi , Louis ! - How did you do that ?
Louis , I 'm going to ask you some questions . Okay , sweetie ?
If the answer is yes , slide the glass to the right .
If it 's no ,
slide it the other way , to the left .
Do you understand ?
Louis , are you okay ?
( GLASS SLIDING )
Are you in pain ?
- ( GASPS ) Oh , my God ! - It 's okay . It 's okay .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
Louis , I brought your chalkboard .
- Remember your chalkboard ? - ( ANNIE CRYING )
Can you write something ?
( JOAN LAUGHS )
Oh , Louis ! I love you , sweetheart !
ANNIE : I 'm sorry . Could we stop ?
What ?
I 'm sorry . Please ... (
STAMMERS )
Louis , we 're going to stop for a second ,
but I 'll be right back .
Are you all right ?
I 'm sorry , I 'm just ... I really ...
I understand , I understand .
That 's exactly how I reacted the first time .
I have to go . Okay . I 'm ... I 'm sorry . Thank you .
- No , no . It 's okay . It 's okay . - Thank you . Yeah .
- I know . I know , honey . - (
BREATHING HEAVILY )
If you want to try this on your own ...
- God ... - It 's okay . It 's okay .
First light the candle ,
then choose an item that belonged to your daughter .
That will be your link . Mine was the chalkboard .
That 's my link .
It 's all right . It 's all right .
- It 's okay . There you go . - (
BREATHING DEEPLY )
Then when you 're ready ,
read this out loud ,
every syllable , very carefully .
(
WHIMPERING ) Sorry , why ? What is it ?
I don 't know what language it is .
The medium had me read it first .
It 's to make things start .
But remember , your whole family ...
Every member needs to be in the house .
Your son , everyone . Very important .
- Okay . - Okay ?
- Deep breath . - ( EXHALES DEEPLY )
You didn 't kill her , Annie .
What ?
She isn 't gone .
- ( TONGUE CLICKS ) - ( GASPS )
( GASPS )
( CRYING )
( ANNIE BREATHING SHAKILY )
( INAUDIBLE )
PETER : Mom ? What are you doing ?
What 's going on ?
You 're sleepwalking .
I 'm sorry . Is Charlie here ?
Why are you scared of me ?
What ?
I never wanted to be your mother .
Why ?
I was scared .
I didn 't feel like a mother . ( SNIFFLES )
But she pressured me .
Then why did you have me ?
It wasn 't my fault . I tried to stop it .
How ?
I tried to have a miscarriage .
However I could .
I did everything they told me not to do but it didn 't work .
I 'm happy it didn 't work .
You tried to kill me .
No , I did not . I love you !
PETER : ( CRYING ) You tried to kill me !
- ANNIE : I love you ! - Why did you try to kill me ?
I didn 't ! I was trying to save you !
- ( MATCH LIGHTS ) - Why did you try to kill me ?
( BOTH CRYING )
( GASPING )
( ANNIE RECITING INDISTINCTLY )
(
WHISPERING ) Peter ?
Peter , sweetheart ? Wake up .
- ( GASPS ) What ? - It 's okay . It 's me .
I am so , so sorry for everything .
- Please , please forgive me . - It 's okay .
I can 't stand the things I said .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
Can you get up , sweetheart ? We 're gonna try something .
I was having a nightmare .
Oh , it 's okay . We can do something .
Do what ?
I figured it out . Come on , come on .
Steven . Baby . Steve , wake up .
- What ? - Come downstairs .
We 're gonna try something together .
Come on , come on .
Steve , come on . Let 's go .
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( ANNIE BREATHING HEAVILY )
( ANNIE CLEARS THROAT )
- Dad ? - It 's okay .
ANNIE : Come on , come on !
( ANNIE EXHALES DEEPLY )
( ANNIE CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY )
Okay . So ...
It 's freezing in here .
ANNIE : Wait ! No , no , no . What are you doing ? Wait !
I 'm gonna close the window .
No , no . We can 't change anything .
I don 't wanna mess it up .
Everyone needs to sit . Come sit .
My friend Joan taught me how to do this .
- (
BREATHES DEEPLY ) - What friend Joan ?
We need our palms on the table
and our fingers to touch . Please .
What are we doing here , Annie ?
Please . You 'll see .
Please . Trust me .
All right , fine .
We can do it over here then .
Peter . Okay .
Okay , Steve . Come on .
I need you both to concentrate .
On what ?
Think about Charlie , if you can .
- Oh , for fuck 's sake . - Sweetheart , please , please .
I tried this 20 minutes ago
- and it worked . - What worked ?
I would not be bringing you down here if it didn 't .
Well , I just need to show you .
- Show what ? - Fuck ! I 'm a ...
I 'm a medium , okay ?
I was seeing apparitions earlier
and I just shook them off and I shouldn 't have .
Please , I know how it sounds ,
but there 's no way to talk about it .
I just need to show you , okay ? Please , you 'll see .
- I 'm completely lucid . - Peter , go to bed .
What ! No , no , no ! Peter , please !
We need to do this as a family .
This needs all our energies , okay ? Together .
- (
BREATHING
HEAVILY ) - All right , I 'll stay .
Steve . Steve , please .
I really , really need you to be open to this .
Please , please . I promise ... Both of you .
Please . I need you to be open . Please .
Come on , Steve . Come on , come on . I promise .
(
BREATHING
HEAVILY ) Okay .
Okay , good .
So , I read that earlier .
I don 't think I need to read that again .
What language is even that ?
(
EXHALES DEEPLY ) Try to concentrate .
Charlie ?
Charlie , are you here ?
Charlie , it 's Mommy .
And Daddy and Peter .
( FLOOR BOARD CREAKS )
Charlie , if you 're in this room with us ,
I 'm gonna have us all touch the glass .
( SOFTLY ) Don 't add pressure .
Now if you 're in here , Charlie ,
I want you to move the glass for us .
Even if it 's just a tiny bit .
- Oh , Jesus Christ , Annie ! - Even if it 's just the tiniest
little movement . Okay , Charlie ?
Okay .
Shit . What the hell ?
- What ? - You don 't feel that ?
What ? Feel what ?
Like , you don 't feel the air flexing ?
Wow ! Yes !
Thank you , Charlie ! That was so good !
Okay . Now , Charlie , what I 'd like for you to do
is I 'd like for you to show them what you did earlier .
( STEVE AND PETER BREATHING HEAVILY )
Can you show them what you just did for me before ?
- Mom . - She 's gonna do it .
- That 's enough ! - What ! No , no , no !
Listen , when I did this earlier ,
this manifested on the page . I saw it !
- I saw it ! - What is it ?
- It 's Charlie ! - Annie !
Charlie , did you want to draw some more ?
- You can keep going . - Stop it ! Stop it !
Okay , we need to keep our fingers touching ...
- ( PETER CRYING ) - You are scaring him !
No , I am not ! Peter , Peter , listen ...
Stop it !
Listen to me . There is no need to be scared .
This is your sister .
Mom .
Charlie , what 's wrong ?
( PETER GASPS )
( ANNIE GROWLING FAINTLY )
( GROWLING STOPS )
( DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE )
( IN CHILD 'S VOICE ) Hello ?
- PETER : Mom ? - ( IN NORMAL VOICE ) Mom ? Mom ?
PETER : I don 't like this .
- Dad , I don 't like this . - ANNIE : What 's happening ?
- Please stop . - Annie , please , stop this .
- What 's going on ? - STEVE : Please stop this .
- Please . - Mom !
You 're really freaking me out . Please stop .
What 's happening ? Why is everyone scared ?
PETER : Dad , make it stop .
(
SHOUTING ) Why are you scaring me !
Make it stop ! Make it stop ! Make it fucking stop !
- PETER : Make it stop ! - (
SCREAMING ) Where 's Mom !
(
SHOUTING ) Stop it ! Stop it now ! Please stop !
Mom ? Peter ? Peter , I 'm scared .
( CRYING ) Dad , make it stop !
( GASPS ) What the hell ? What are you doing ?
( PETER CRYING )
What happened ?
( DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE )
TEACHER : Our country has had many ups and downs
economically speaking .
We 've talked about the struggles
during the 1800s compared to the fall of 1929 ,
in an era that become known appropriately
as the Great Depression .
For a decade we suffered through many , many hardships .
In 1929 , Wall Street had been going so well
that when it finally crashed because of the Great Boom ,
it caused a huge decline in the economy .
So much so that it caused food lines .
( TEACHER SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY )
This is where the Federal Government has ,
or still has ...
(
TEACHER
CONTINUES
SPEAKING )
( TONGUE CLICKS )
Uh , uh . Yes , Peter ?
Um , I 'm sorry . I have to go to the bathroom .
Um , of course . Take the pass .
As I was saying ...
( PHONE
RINGING )
Hello ?
STEVE : Can you guess who just called me from school
in complete hysterics ?
- Charlie ? - What ?
Uh , nothing . What happened ?
Peter just called me , Annie ,
terrified , crying in the halls ,
convinced he 's being threatened
by some vengeful spirit .
Why does he think he 's being threatened ?
Listen to me , Annie . I have a son to protect .
What does that mean ?
It means that that 's what I 'm worried about right now
and that 's how ...
Hey , don 't talk to me like this .
- He 's my son too ... - ( LINE
DISCONNECTS )
Oh !
- ( GRUNTS ) - ( PHONE BEEPS )
Do not hang up on me again .
I am not sleepwalking anymore . Do you understand ?
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( PHONE CLATTERS )
( PHONE RINGING )
AUTOMATED VOICE : At the tone ,
please record your voice message .
When you are finished recording ,
you may hang up or press pound for more options .
- ( BEEPS ) - MAN : Annie , hi !
This is Patrick at the Archer Gallery .
Um , I was just calling first to see how you 're doing ,
how your family 's doing .
We 've all been thinking about you
and just worrying about you
and hoping you 're okay .
You guys have been in our constant thoughts and prayers .
And then also , uh , we just wanted to , well , to say first ,
if you need us to postpone the show or push the date ,
it 's obviously more than okay .
And if not , uh , we just wanna call and see
if we could help in any way or offer ...
- (
GASPING ) - (
PATRICK
CONTINUES
SPEAKING )
( SCREAMS )
STEVE : Oh , jeez . That smell .
( EXHALES )
STEVE : Annie ? What 's that smell ?
What the fuck happened here ?
I didn 't feel like looking at it anymore .
( SIGHS )
( FAINT SCRIBBLING )
( SCRIBBLING CONTINUES )
( SCRIBBLING GETS LOUDER )
( TONGUE CLICKS )
Charlie ?
( THUDS )
( DOG GROWLING )
( WHIMPERS )
( CONTINUES GROWLING )
( GRUNTING )
( BARKS )
( CHOKING )
- ( DOOR SLAMS ) - ( DOG YELPS )
ANNIE : Peter ? Oh my God , Peter !
( PETER GASPING )
What 's wrong , baby ? What 's happening ?
What are you doing ?
What do you mean ?
You were pulling on my head !
What ? No I wasn 't . I just came in .
You were screaming . What happened ?
I saw Charlie in the corner
and then you started trying to pull my head off !
Oh , Peter . I would never do that to you .
Are you crazy ? Please , baby .
( PANTING )
What corner did you see Charlie ?
( SHUDDERING )
Peter , listen to me .
I don 't know what 's happening or what you just saw ,
but I am stopping this .
Do not tell Dad what you just said to me .
Do not , okay ? Because it is not true .
Something is happening
and I 'm the only one who could stop it .
Do you understand ? I 'm the only one
who can fix this .
( WIND BLOWING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( FIRE CRACKLING )
( GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
ANNIE : Joan ?
( KNOCKING FRANTICALLY )
Joan , please . I need to talk to you .
Joan , I really need to ask you a question .
Joan !
( GASPS )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER )
WOMAN : ( IN
DISTANCE ) Peter !
Peter !
I expel you !
Zantany !
( INAUDIBLE CONVERSATIONS )
Dagdany !
Aparagon !
(
SHOUTING LOUDER ) Peter !
Get out !
Peter !
( PANTING )
- ( GRUNTS ) - (
BOTTLES RATTLE )
( OBJECTS RATTLE )
( PANTING HEAVILY )
Oh , God .
( CONTINUES PANTING )
( ANNIE CRYING )
( LAPTOP CHIMES )
( MOUSE CLICKS )
- (
GROANING ) - ( FLIES
BUZZING )
( ROD CLATTERS )
( GROANS )
( BUZZING CONTINUES )
( GROANING )
... so everyone feels justified .
Iphigenia 's murder was commanded by the gods .
- ( FLIES
CONTINUE
BUZZING ) - (
GASPING )
( GASPS )
( RETCHING AND COUGHING )
TEACHER : So , really , Agamemnon had no choice ...
(
TEACHER
CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY )
( TONGUE CLICKING )
( TONGUE CLICKING CONTINUES )
Peter .
Peter , what 's wrong ?
Peter , are you all right ?
( TONGUE CLICKING )
- BRIDGET : Can he breathe ? - (
GROANING
FAINTLY )
Peter , what are you doing , man ?
( SCREAMS )
( SCREAMING )
( PHONE RINGING )
( CLOCK TICKING )
( PHONE CONTINUES RINGING )
AUTOMATED VOICE : Call from West High School .
( PHONE RINGING )
Hello .
Yes , it is .
( TYRES SCREECHING )
( SIGHS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SOBBING )
( CRYING ) Oh , thank God .
Wait , what ? Oh my God !
What happened ? What happened to him ?
Oh , no , no , no , no , no . ( GASPING )
Oh my God . Oh , no . Oh , who did that ?
He did it , apparently , to himself .
( STEVE SIGHS )
Smashed his face into his own desk .
Okay , Steve . Wait , wait . Wait , Steve . Listen .
STEVE : Take his feet . Please , take his feet .
( GRUNTING )
Steve , uh , upstairs ...
In the attic when you were gone , I went up there and I ...
I just ... I really need you
to go up there and see what I saw .
There 's a body .
Yeah . I mean , I think it 's my mother ,
I think , but I can 't tell because the skin 's all black
and she 's all distended but the head is gone . ( CRYING )
Will you , please ? I just need you to go and see upstairs .
( ANNIE SOBBING )
( SHUDDERING ) Please , Steve .
( PANTING )
And then there 's more .
You mean more than your mother 's headless body ?
Of course there is .
- ( GASPS ) - (
INSECTS
BUZZING )
( PANTING )
( STEVE SCREAMS )
- Jesus , fuck ! - Okay , there 's more .
What the fuck was that ?
Why didn 't you call the police ?
The police can 't help us .
Who the fuck is that up there ?
Do you remember Joan , my friend whose grandson died ?
- She took me to her apartment . - It did look like your mother .
Well , listen . She taught me how to do the séance .
I didn 't even want to , but she brought her grandson back
and I saw it and felt it just like you did with Charlie .
Now , look . This is my mother 's album .
Now look here . See this ?
See her ? That 's her . That 's Joan .
She didn 't even mention knowing my mom
and I 've never met her before , but she approached me .
She consoled me .
She told me about this séance , and she showed me how .
Now look at this . See this symbol ?
On the necklace my mom gave me .
It 's her necklace , right ? They 're both wearing it ,
and they 're wearing it in every photo .
And look at that pattern ! Did you see up there ?
This was painted above the body , right ?
In blood !
You dug up the grave . It was you , wasn 't it ?
What ?
All those nights you were
pretending to go to the movies .
You 're not even listening !
And then the day the cemetery called , I said ,
" Oh , I won 't tell her because she 'd be worried . "
Oh , God damn it ! Listen to me , Steve !
I know you don 't trust me
and there is nothing I can do about that .
But they put a curse on us when we brought Charlie back .
We made a pact with something .
Something that is in this house .
I don 't know what it is but it is after Peter .
I watched these pages fill .
All of them are Peter !
I 'm sorry . I don 't know what I did .
I don 't know what I did but Peter is in danger ...
And I started it .
Now if we destroy this book ,
it will take me too .
I tried to burn it . I tried .
But my arm caught on fire on its own
as if I was linked to it because I am linked to it .
I understand this now . Please !
If we don 't destroy this book ...
( CRYING )
Peter will ...
Oh , God . Do you understand ?
We have to do this . Please , please , please , please .
For Peter .
I need you to trust me , Steve .
It needs to be me . It 's my fault .
It 's my fault . I know it 's my fault . Please .
Please , I need you to throw it in the fire .
Please , I just ... I can 't do it .
I can 't . I 'm just too fucking scared .
But if we don 't do it ...
If we don 't do it , it 's gonna be Peter ,
it 's gonna be our son . Okay , I know this . I know so .
Just , please , please , please , please , please ...
(
CONTINUES CRYING )
Steve , please . Please understand , baby .
Please , please . Please throw it in the fire .
( SNIFFLES )
Sweetheart , please .
Please take it , take it . You gotta do it .
You gotta do it .
Okay . Thank you , thank you .
Okay , here . Okay .
Now listen to me . Listen to me .
( SOBBING QUIETLY )
Oh ! You are the love of my life .
I love you , Steve . I love you so , so much .
Oh , God , I love you so much .
And I love Peter so much .
( PANTING )
Now please , just ...
Please just throw it in .
( GASPING )
I 'm not gonna do this with you anymore .
What ? No , no , no !
No , no , it 's not helpful for you .
You are sick , Annie .
I need to call the police .
Oh , God !
( GASPS )
( SCREAMING )
( GROANS )
Mom ?
Dad ?
( FAINT FOOTSTEPS RUNNING )
( INSECT CHIRRING INTERMITTENTLY )
( FLIES BUZZING )
Mom ?
Dad ?
( LOUD BANG )
( CLATTERING )
( FLIES BUZZING )
PETER : Hello ?
( FLOORBOARD CREAKING )
( DOOR SHUTS )
- ( CLOCK
TICKING ) - ( FIRE
CRACKLING )
Mom ?
( GASPING )
( WOOD CREAKING )
( THUDS )
( PETER WHIMPERING )
( ANNIE SCREAMS )
( RAPID KNOCKING )
Stop ! Mom , please stop !
Mom , I 'm sorry ! Okay , I 'm sorry .
( RAPID KNOCKING CONTINUES )
( SOBBING )
Mommy . Mommy , please . I 'm begging you .
I 'm begging you to stop .
( KNOCKING STOPS )
- (
GASPING ) - ( FLIES
BUZZING )
Mommy ?
( GASPS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Just gotta wake up . ( MUMBLES )
You just gotta wake up . Come on . You 're okay .
Just wake up . Wake up ! Wake up ! Wake up !
( SNIFFLES )
( FLESH TEARING AND SQUELCHING )
- ( CLINKS ) - ( SAWING
CONTINUES )
( SCREAMS )
( THUDS )
( SAWING CONTINUES )
( SAWING STOPS )
( THUDDING )
( INSECTS CHIRPING )
( TONGUE CLICKS )
JOAN : Oh , hey , hey , hey . It 's all right .
Charlie ...
You 're all right now .
You are Paimon ,
one of the eight kings of Hell .
We have looked to the Northwest
and called you in .
We 've corrected your first female body
and give you now this healthy male host .
We reject the Trinity and pray devoutly to you , great Paimon .
Give us your knowledge of all secret things .
Bring us honor , wealth , and good familiars .
Bind all men to our will ,
as we have bound ourselves for now and ever to yours .
( FOOTSTEPS )
Hail , Paimon !
WORSHIPPERS : Hail , Paimon !
Hail !
Improved By : FidelPerez Sub Upload Date : August 22 , 2018